Toni Morrison Papers, 1957-: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Writings, 1929 September-2015; 100 boxes (3 partial)
  - Phase 2: Other Writings, 1958-2001; 1 item
    - Miscellaneous Drafts From Fire, undated; 1 item
      Includes drafts of letters, speeches, and notes. The opening lines of Love appear in one notepad.
    - "Graham Greene--Notes", circa 1950s?; 1 item
    - Biographical Notes, undated; 1 item
    - Journal Entries, 1958-2001; 1 item
    - Treatment Idea for Huck Finn, 1983; 1 item
    - Princeton Office of Physical Planning, circa 1990s; 1 item
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1953-2015; 35 boxes (2 partial)
  - 70th Birthday Cards, 2001; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - 75th Birthday Guest Book, 2006; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - 80th Birthday Cards, 2011; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - A, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 67, Folder 4-5)
  - Abinader, Elmaz, 1986-1990; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Achebe, Chinua, 1991-2005; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Adams, Eve, 2004-2007; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Adero, Malaika, 1996-2007; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Ahearn, Eileen, 1979-2008; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Al Abdullah, Queen Raina, 2004; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Allen, Danielle, 2002-2013; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Allende, Isabel, 1987-2001; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Al Muhammad, Princess Firyal, 2013; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Als, Hilton, 2000-2003; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Annan, Kofi and Nane, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Angelou, Maya, 1994-2013; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Appiah, Anthony, 1990; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Asaro, Sal, 1997-2009; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Atanasoff, Jeanne, 1988-2015; 2 folders (Box 68, Folder 11-12)
    Includes photographs.
  - Atlas, James, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - B, 1986-2015; 3 folders (Box 69, Folder 1-3)
  - Bach, Jean, 1992; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Bailey, Donna, 1982-2009; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Baker, Houston and Charlotte, 1987-1992; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Baldwin, Emma Berdis Jones, 1977-1999; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Baldwin, James, 1976, 1986; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Bambara, Toni Cade, 1977-1995; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 1, Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Banfield, Bill, 2002, undated; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Banks, Russell, 1990-2002; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Baraka, Amiri and Amina, 1981-2004; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Batton, Susan Sayre, 1990-1994; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Belafonte, Harry, 1990; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Bell, Derrick, 1990-1996; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Benham, Joan A., 1999-2001; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Berg, Joel, 1982-2013; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Bergman, Robert and Laurie McCannel, 1997-2010; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Bernstein, Robert L., 1988-2002; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Bertolino, James, 1983; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Bezos, Mackenzie Tuttle, 1990-2014; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Bhabha, Homi, 1994-2011; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Bonetti, Kay, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Bourgois, Christian and Dominique, 1988-2000; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Bowen, William, 1987-1998; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Boyle, Kay, 1984-1987; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Bracey, Phyllis Woods, 1988-2003; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Contains a photo
  - Bradley, Bill, 1994-1996; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Breitwieser, Mitch, 1988-1991; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Brombert, Beth and Victor, 1989-2008; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Brony, Elizabeth, 1995-1997; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Brooks, Cynthia, 1999, undated; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Brooks, Georgia, 1971-2011; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Brooks, Gwendolyn, 1993-1997; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Brooks, Lois Wofford, 1982-2005; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 1, Box 71, Folder 12-13)
  - Brown, Carlene, 1977-2012; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Bruckner, Carol, undated; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Bush, Barbara, 1989; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Busia, Abena, 1985-2011; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Byatt, A.S., 1994-2001; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - C, 1977-2015; 2 folders (Box 72, Folder 7-8)
  - Cammerzell, Frederick, 1988-2008; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Caro, Robert, 1993; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Carpenter, Lea, 2003-2013; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Carrasco, David, 1991-2013; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Carroll, Doris, 1980-1995; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Carter, Graydon, 2001-2011; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Carter, Rosalynn and Jimmy, 1980-2009; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Casebere, James, 2008-2012; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Cepeda, Patricia, 1998-2000; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Champ, Norman B., 1987-1992; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Cheatwood, Kiarri T-H., 1981-1989; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Cheever, Susan, 1984-1985, undated; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Cisneros, Sandra, 1998 January 20; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Clark, Ana Steele and John, 1986-2011; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Clark, Larry, 1986; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Clemons, Dolores, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Clinton, Bill and Hillary, 1993-2006; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Clinton, Bill and Hillary--White House Invitations, 1993-2000; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Coetzee, J.M., 2004; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Cole, Johnetta B., 1995, undated; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Conarroe, Joel, 2005; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Conner, Marc, 2001-2005; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Cook, Beverly and Charles, 1988-1993; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Cooper, Bill, Clarissa, Ashley and Courtney, 2003-undated; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Cornell, Drucilla, 1993-2007; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Cosby, Bill and Camille, 1986-1997; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Couric, Katie, 2012; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Curasi, Anne, 2009-2012; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - D, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 74, Folder 12-13)
  - d'Amboise, Jacques, 1987-2012; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Daniel, Clifton, 1983; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Danielpour, Richard, 2002-2007; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Danticat, Edwidge, 2014; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Davis, Eisa, 2005-2011; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Davis, Natalie Zemon, 1992-2013; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Davis, Thadious, 1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Dee, Ruby and Ossie Davis, 1992-2012; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Dees, Morris, 2004; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - DeCrow, Karen, 1988-2006; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Demme, Jonathan, 1997-1999; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Denard, Carolyn, 1991-2015; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - DiFilippo, Rosemary, 1991-2014; 2 folders (Box 75, Folder 6-7)
  - Dimock, Peter, 1985-2010; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Dimock, Wai-Chee, 1985-1994; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Dinkins, David and Joyce, 1989-2007; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Dixon, Melvin, 1977-1987; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Doctorow, E.L., 2001; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Dorfman, Ariel, 1986-2002; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Dorris, Michael and Louise Erdrich, 1985-1993; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Dubois, Laurent, 1992-2005; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - E, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Elias, Robert and Helen, 1953-2013; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Ellison, Ralph and Fanny, undated; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - English, Lady Judith, 2005; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Epstein, Barbara, 2000; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Epstein, Jason, 1998-2003; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - F, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 76, Folder 14-15)
  - Fabre, Geneviève, 1992-2007; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Fagles, Robert and Lynne, 1994-2008; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Farrow, Mia, 1995-1997; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Faust, Drew, 2001, undated; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Featherston, Natalie, 2004-2010; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Ferris, William, 1997-2009; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Fishkin, Shelley Fisher, 1992-2000; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Florio, Jim, 1993; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Forbes, Sheila, undated; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Forrest, Leon and Anne, 1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Foster, Jodie, 1985-1993; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1986-1992; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Freedgood, Anne, 1980-1994; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Freedgood, Julia, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Frelinghuysen, Barrett, 2000-2013; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Freund, Gerald, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Fulmer, Jackie, 1997-2003; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Fultz, Lucille, 1989-2015; 2 folders (Box 77, Folder 11-12)
  - G, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 77, Folder 13-14)
  - Gaines, Kevin, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Gass, William, 1985-1993; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Gates, Henry Louis, 1983-2008; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Gerzina, Gretchen Holbrook, 1986-2007; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Giddings, Paula, 1974-2009; 2 folders (Box 78, Folder 5-6)
  - Gilbert, Sandra, 1989-2005; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Ginsburg, Rachel and Philip, 1989-2012; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Giovanni, Nikki, 1989-2014; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Glasser, Barbara, 1988-2010; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Goellner, Ellen, 1992-2015; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Goerner, Lee, 1987-circa 1992; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Goheen, Margaret and Robert, 1988-2008; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Gordimer, Nadine, 1985-2002; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Gornick, Vivian, 1990; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Graham, Billy, 2000-2011; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Graham, Maryemma, 2005-2015; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Grant, Alice, 1984-2003; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Grauer, Rhoda, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Greaves, William, 1988-2005; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Gregorian, Vartan, 1987-2012; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Griffin, Farah Jasmine, 2003-2013; 2 folders (Box 79, Folder 7-8)
  - Grosvenor, Vertamae, 1979-1994; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Groth, Patricia, 1985-1995; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Gubar, Susan, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Guénif-Souilamas, Nacira, 2007; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Gunn, Bill, 1984; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Gutmann, Amy, 2000-2012; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - H, 1970-2015; 2 folders (Box 79, Folder 15-16)
  - Haba, Jim and Erica, 1998-2007; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Hale, Janet Campbell, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Harper, Conrad and Marsha, 1987-2008; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Harper, Michael S., 1975-2003; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Haskell, Molly, 1987-1994; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Hayes, Jennifer and Graham, 1996-2011; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Heaney, Seamus, 1996-1998; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Heiskell, Andrew, 1986-1996; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Hendricks, Obery, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Herrin, Judith, 1992-1995; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Hickey, Meghan, 1996-2004; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Higginbotham, Jr., A. Leon, 1978-1998; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Hinton, William, 1984-1999; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Hodsoll, Frank, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Holbrook, Hal, 2014; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Holt, Rush, 2012; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - hooks, bell, 1997; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Hoppenthaler, John, 2000, undated; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Houston, Pam, 2003-2006; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Howe, Florence, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - I, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - J, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Jacobozzi, Vivian, 1990-1997; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Johnson, Beth and Franklin, 1993, undated; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Jones, Bill T., 2002-2006; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Jones, Patricia Spears, 2004-2005; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Jones, Quincy, 1986-2006; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Jong, Erica, 1995-2012; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Jordan, June, 1974-2002; 2 folders (Box 81, Folder 4-5)
  - Joseph, Peter and Wendy, 1997-2006; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - K, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Kadish, Rachel, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Kaess, Lisa, circa 2008-2010; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Kebede, Alitash, 1984-1987; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Kenan, Randall, 1985-1992; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Kennedy, Adrienne, 1984-1992; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Kennedy, Randall, 1994-2003; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Kennedy, William, 1985-1994; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Killian, Karl, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Kilroy, Tom and Dotty, 1993-1996, undated; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Kilson, Martin, 1996; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - King, Marion, 1988-1995; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Kingston, M. Ray, 1994; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Kingston, Maxine Hong, 1984-1993; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Knopf, Helen, 1981-1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Krantz, Bertha, 1988-1992; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Krementz, Jill, 1994-1996; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Krislov, Marvin, 2009-2015; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Kwayana, Tchaiko, 1988-2010; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - L, 1970-2015; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Lacour, Claudia Brodsky, 1990-2015; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Ladd, Florence, 1989-2011; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Lambrinidis, Christiana, 2007-2014; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Lebowitz, Fran, 2000-2011; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - LeClerc, Paul, 2004-2006, undated; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Lee, Chang-Rae, 2004-2009; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Lee, Spike, 1986-1999; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Leenders, Rada, 2005-2007; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Leland, Christopher T., 1983-1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Lemaître, Pascal, 2005; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Lewis, Robin, 1989-1998; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Lewis, Shirley A. R., 2006-2009; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Lieberman, Erez, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Lightfoot, Betty, 2003-2012; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Lish, Gordon, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Loggia, Marjorie, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Lombard, Rudy, 1980-2014; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Love, Edward, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 10)
    Includes slides.
  - Lubiano, Wahneema, 1991-1999; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - M, 1970-2012; 4 folders (Box 83, Folder 12-15)
  - Ma, Yo Yo, 1995; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Madden, Chris, 1999-2012; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Maguire, Mary, undated; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Maillard, Carol, 1984-2012; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Malkiel, Nancy and Burton, 1993-2009; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Mandela, Nelson, 1993; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Massiah, Louis, 1998-2015; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Matsutsuyu, Emiko, 1996-2000; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Mayes, Janis, 1988-2011; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Maynard, Valerie, 1988-1997; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - McBride, Dwight, 1990-2008; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - McCluskey, John, 1984-1989; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - McCourt, Frank, 2008; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - McCoy, Maureen, 1987-2000; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - McDonald, Erroll and Klara Glowczewska, 2001-2010; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - McFadden, Bernice, 2000-2011; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - McGowan, Tara, 1993, 2002; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - McKay, Nellie, 1981-1990; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - McKayle, Donald, 1981-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - McMillan, Terry, 1986-1990; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - McPherson, James, 1987-1991; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Medina, Kate, 1988-2008; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Merwin, W.S., 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Middleton, Joyce, 1990-1994; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Milanés, Cecilia Rodríguez, 1989-2008; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Milford, Nancy, 1988-1993; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Miller, Robin J., 2004; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Millett, Kate, 1990; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Cards, 1989-2015; 5 folders (Box 86, Folder 1-5, Box 87, Folder 1-3)
  - Miscellaneous Invitations, 1985-2000; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Mondale, Joan, 1979; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Moore, Beatrice Duncan, 1996-2008; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Morgenroth, Kate, 1998-2001; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Mori, Aoi, 2001-2009; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Morrison, Cecilia Rouse, 2000-2012; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Morrison, Harold and Claudette, 1993, undated; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Morrison, Harold Ford, 1979-2011; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Morrison, Mavis, 1973-1994; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Morrison, Nidal and Safa, 2002-2009; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Morrison, Slade, 1981-2007, undated; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Moses, Gilbert, 1986-1993; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Moskin, J. Robert, 1988; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Mosley, Walter, 1998-2005; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Muldoon, Paul and Jean Hanff Korelitz, 1993-2007; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - N, 1971-2006; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Nabokov, Ivan, 1988-2006; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Nagy, Bob and Vincy, 1998-2009; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Navasky, Victor, 1986-2005; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Naylor, Gloria, 1984-1986; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Nesbit, Lynn, 1989, undated; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Newhouse, Donald and Susan, 1987-2007; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Newhouse, Elyse and Michael, 1992-1995; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Nick, Larry, 1988-2003; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Noormohamed, Taleeb, 1996-1999; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Norman, Jessye, 1990-2015; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - O, 1981-2005; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol, 1983-2008; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Obama, Barack and Michelle, 2009-2012; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Obama Campaign, 2008-2014; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Oe, Kenzaburo, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Ohkoso, Yoshiko, 1993-circa 2008; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Ondaatje, Michael, 1994-2002; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Ostriker, Alicia and Jeremiah, 1996-2000; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Owens, Joan Murrell and Frank, 1984-2011; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - P, 1970-2015; 2 folders (Box 90, Folder 8-9)
  - Pagels, Elaine, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Painter, Nell, 1988-2013; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Paladino, Vita, 2004-2012; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Pardini, Patti, 1984-1987; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Paquet-Deyris, Anne-Marie, 1988-2007; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Patterson, Louise and MaryLouise, 1987-2000; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Pelosi, Nancy, 2012; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Pemberton, Gayle, 1987-1999; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Pierce-Baker, Charlotte, 1990-1998; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Pinckney, Darryl, 2002; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Piñon, Nélida, 1988-1998; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Pinter, Harold, 2005; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Plimpton, George, 1992; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Pohlig, Ulrike, 1987-1992; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Polinsky, Eugene, 2001-2014; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Powell, Marc and Ivy, 2004-2008; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Price, Reynolds, 1974-2008; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Price, Richard, 1985-1990; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Q, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Quinn, Alice, 1993-2003; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - R, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 91, Folder 17-18)
  - Raboteau, Albert and Julia, 1993, undated; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Rampersad, Arnold, 1988-2006; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Reagon, Bernice Johnson, 1984-2006; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Reed, Ishmael, 1977-2007; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Reid, Harry, 2012; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Reidy, Carolyn, 2003-2006; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Remnick, David, 1998-2009; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Rhinehart, Doug, 1988; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 5)
    Includes photographs
  - Richardson, Yvette, 1978-1998; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Rigolot, Carol and François, 1990-2002; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Riley, Mary, 2011, undated; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Roberts, Mary, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Robinson, Lisa, 1995-2009; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Roediger, Dave, 1994-1997; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Roth, Philip, 1985; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Rouse, Carolyn and Glenn, 2012, undated; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Rouse, Lorraine and Carl, 2001-2015; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Rudenstine, Neil and Angelica, 1988-2005; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Rushdie, Salman, 1994-2000; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - S, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 92, Folder 17-18, Box 93, Folder 1-2)
  - Said, Edward, 1992; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Samuels, Wilfred D., 1988-2001; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Sanchez, Sonia, 1993-2014; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Saunders, Paula Redick and George, 1988-2015; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Saunders, Raymond, 1989-1995; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Saunders, Ronnie, 1987-1994; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Sawyer, Diane, 2005; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Scearce, J. Mark, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Schwartz, Leonard, 1997-2008; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Scrivanich, Olivia Brooks, 1984-2008; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 12)
    Toni Morrison's Niece
  - Seward, Adrienne Lanier, 2001; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Shalit, Willa, 1986-2005; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Shapiro, Harold and Vivian, 1990-2001; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Shestakova, Tatyana, 2003-2008; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Showalter, Elaine, 1990-1992; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Silko, Leslie Marmon, 1984-1999; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Simmons, Ruth, 1988-2012; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Simone, Nina, 1995; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Smalls, Alexander, 1995-2000; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Smart, Aisha Karefa, 1988-2007; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Smart, Gloria Karefa, 1986-2014; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Smart, Kali-Ma Karefa, 1995-2010; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Smiley, Tavis, 2006, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Barbara, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Liz, 2008-2010; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Soyinka, Wole, 1994; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Spillers, Hortense, 1975-1989; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Spivak, Gayatri, 1995-2006; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Stansell, Christine, 1989-1995; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Stein, Sol, 2003-2004; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Stewart, Connie Jellison, 1984-2010; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Strick, Joe, 1985-2001; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Strouse, Jean, 1987-1990; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Suber, Gloria, 1981-2009; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Swain, Carol, 1989-1997; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - T, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Talese, Nan, 2002; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Talley, Andre Leon, 2012; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 6)